{
    "id": "f595c068c41542c7a8dc9c92900110da",
    "title": "Determiners Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I would like to ask ……………………… questions.",
            "description": "Use a few to refer to a small number.",
            "answers": [
                "few",
                "a few",
                "the few"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "8ab78fa837b84027b0e5868bd77fcf90"
        },
        {
            "question": "I didn’t find …………………………… there.",
            "description": "Use any, anyone, anybody, anything etc. in questions and negatives. ",
            "answers": [
                "no one",
                "anyone",
                "someone"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "4a4d26a9d25e4fc8b9e5a97ce7c0cd0a"
        },
        {
            "question": "Very …………………………… politicians are really honest.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "few",
                "a few",
                "the few"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "276d1c4e2f8a4186be396c3df111977a"
        },
        {
            "question": "Only ………………………… politicians are really honest.",
            "description": "There is not much difference between only a few and very few.",
            "answers": [
                "few",
                "a few",
                "the few"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "3edab4f5c2164cdc8d219a38990b4f7d"
        },
        {
            "question": "………………………… agreed to come with me.",
            "description": "Either someone or no one is possible here. Note that the meanings are different. ",
            "answers": [
                "Someone",
                "Anyone",
                "No one"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "7cbc6fff5c7442d99956ebf3f3f04d37"
        },
        {
            "question": "She doesn’t have ………………………… friends.",
            "description": "Use many before a plural noun.",
            "answers": [
                "many",
                "much"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "31f9eff4fd784cdcaba53423d85c63f4"
        },
        {
            "question": "I had …………………………… to help me.",
            "description": "No one means the same as not anyone.",
            "answers": [
                "anyone",
                "no one"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "cf96effbfb854fa1be1786fefd95b974"
        },
        {
            "question": "There are …………………………….. birds on the tree.",
            "description": "Use some in affirmative sentences. ",
            "answers": [
                "some",
                "any"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "d58ee2ef01524eb4a5bcc891bf788669"
        },
        {
            "question": "Does …………………………. know the answer?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "someone",
                "anyone",
                "no one"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "45cf3d69f99846bfba6b1925f8e72b10"
        },
        {
            "question": "I would like to find …………………………… books on western philosophy.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "some",
                "any"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "22173bca55624c06926f6cbdcedd28d8"
        },
        {
            "question": "I don’t have ……………………….. money.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "many",
                "much"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "4fa841ca554d46df95be36945da1dd08"
        },
        {
            "question": "Does ………………………. know where she lives?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "anybody",
                "somebody",
                "nobody"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "af669e25bea84124938bcb5737d9a89b"
        }
    ]
}